

## Profile

Energetic software engineer with 3+ years' experience developing robust code for high-volume businesses. I'm amiable, articulate, confident and ambitious personality with a strong desire to make an excellent impact in Information Communication Technology based on a personal ability to take on task and overcome challenges through team building and team work that is anchored on ell ective communication and an excellent interpersonal relationship that is focused on the achievement of set objectives and corporate goals.

# Employment History

Software Developer at Cardinal Stone Registrars, Ebute Metta

December 2019 — Present

Develop, Maintain And Deployment of new and existing software solutions for the company.

Full-stack Developer(Contract) at FBIS Technologies Limited, Ikoyi September 2019 — December 2019

Design,Implementation and deployment of Interswitch payment SDK for their mobile solutions(Java).

#### Web Developer at Kurtiva limited, ikoyi

August 2018 — August 2019

- Researched, designed, implemented and documented scalable back-end, front-end web applications for an online gaming app
- Ensured team of developers followed software quality guidelines on all projects managed.
- Lead and manage activities of a team of highly talented remote software developers using scrum agile framework.
- Interfaced with business analysts, developers and technical support to determine the best requirement specifications.
- Presented over 125 effective ideas for system improvements.

### Web Developer at Ulinxs System Networks, Lagos

February 2017 — July 2018

- Led a team of 4 developers charged with the responsibility of prototyping, developing and maintaining all client projects for the company
- Researched, designed, implemented and documented a commercial application for competency assessment using PHP with Laravel framework for a client, and the software helped the client grow their client base by over 30%.
- Trained new developers and programmers on company standards for design and review.

#### **Details**

08026425250 seyiolawepo@gmail.com

#### **Skills**

HTML, CSS, PHP/Laravel, javascript and MySQL (3+ years)

Java, Springboot Framework (3+years)

Git Management (3+ years)

Vue Js, Angular js

Business Process Management(Process Maker)

Leadership

Collaboration

Dedicated team player

Agile Project Management

**Critical Thinking** 

**Software Testing** 

#### Links

linkedin
Cardinal Stone E-Accreditation
Portal
Wixio Gaming
vouchernet(Laravel)
mallfy (Laravel)
Etuk(php, jquery,html, css)
optisoft/fitc(laravel, php,
jquery,html, css)
GPACalc(java, xml, sqlite)
Task it(java, xml, realm)
fixerwithin (Laravel)
reciprada(Laravel)

#### **Hobbies**

Music, Sports and Exercise, Cooking, Writing

 Met with management to provide detailed project reports and milestone updates.

Office Assistant / Member Web Information Systems development and maintenance team at Federal Government College Ogbomosho, Oyo

October 2015 — November 2016

- Perform regular ollice duties which includes but is not limited to preparing ollicial Ollice documents among others, create, manage and maintain information systems for school use, e.t.c
- Tested websites and performed troubleshooting prior to deployment.

# Education

# Bachelor of Science(Computer Science), Kwara State University, Malete, Ilorin

August 2011 — May 2015

Senate President, National Association of Computer Science Students Kwara State University Chapter

West African School Certificate (WAEC), Blessed Assurance College, Alimosh, Lagos

August 2004 — March 2009

First School Leaving Certificate (FSLC), St. Thomas Aquinas Primary Schools, Lagos

March 1997 — March 2003

## Courses

Diploma in Enterprise Application Development(Java), NIIT

February 2014 — January 2015

Computer appreciation, FlorinTech Institute

February 2009 — July 2010

# Internships

# Computer Lab. Technician at NIIT, Lagos

May 2014 — December 2014

- Support computer lab operations.
- Support faculty and students to use computer soware and hardware.
- Respond to queries and introduce students to use of computers and peripheral equipment.
- Log equipment damage and malfunctions.
- Extend assistance towards computers and printers' support.
- Clean, review and handle minor equipment maintenance to assure its operational condition.

# ■ References

References available upon request